Speiser Shumate Geoghan Krause & Rheingold Records
Speiser Shumate Geoghan Krause & Rheingold Records
1956-1971
Speiser, Shumate, Geoghan, Krause & Rheingold.
58.5 linear ft.
Papers of the New York City law firm, specializing in transportation law as it relates to commercial aviation. Collection includes accident reports, associated case files, Civil Aernonautics Board hearings materials, correspondence, memoranda, press releases, research and technical information, clippings, depositions, and exhibits entered as evidence. Also, material related to Stuart M. Speiser's lobbying efforts to obtain revision of the 1929 Warsaw Convention on international aviation, specifically his efforts to demonstrate the need for unlimited liability of carriers in international crashes.
148679
Biographical History
Speiser Shumate Geoghan Krause & Rheingold was a New York City law firm, specializing in transportation law as it related to commercial aviation. Among other things the firm has acted as counsel for plaintiffs seeking damages in air crashes.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Speiser Shumate Geoghan Krause & Rheingold Records consist of case files and a section relating to the Warsaw Convention's provisions on international aviation and carrier liability.
The Case files consist of materials relating to specific airplane crashes and the resulting investigations and/or litigation. The cases are organized alphabetically, either by the name of the first party to a suit or, in cases where no suit was brought, by the name of the airline whose plane was involved in an accident. Most cases are also identified by a Civil Aeronautics Board docket number. Case file materials are subdivided within each case into two sections labeled General and Evidence. The general material includes accident reports, associated cases, Civil Aeronautics Board Hearing materials, correspondence, discovery materials, memoranda, research and technical information, clippings, and the like. Evidence consists of depositions and exhibits. The depositions are organized alphabetically by the surname of the individual who gave the testimony. Transcripts of depositions are present, as well as some supporting materials, which were apparently used in preparing questions for the witnesses. The exhibits consist largely of reproductions of various airline company records which were introduced as evidence. These are usually arranged in the original numbered series, although some exhibits were unnumbered and have been so labeled. Case files, 1972 additions contains additional case files acquired in 1972; these have not been integrated with the rest of the collection.
The Warsaw Convention materials stem from Stuart M. Speiser's role in attempting in the 1960s to obtain a revision of the 1929 Warsaw Convention on international aviation. Mr. Speiser took a leading role in a lobbying effort to convince federal policy-makers of the need for unlimited liability of the carrier in international crashes. Included here are correspondence, memoranda, press releases, newspaper clippings, magazine separates, writings, as well as materials from the Civil Aeronautics Board, the Interagency Group on International Aviation, the International Civil Aviation Organization, the U.S. Senate Foreign Relations Committee and other organizations. Among the correspondence in this section are incoming letters from a number of United States Senators, including J. William Fulbright, Everett Dirksen and Hubert Humphrey.
Arrangement of the Collection
Case files are organized alphabetically, either by the name of the first party to a suit or, in cases where no suit was brought, by the name of the airline whose plane was involved in the accident. 1972 additions are listed in the inventory by docket number, although the material physically remains in original order as received. Warsaw Convention materials are arranged alphabetically.
Subject and Genre Headings
Speiser, Stuart M.; Spieser, Shumate, Geoghan, Krause & Rheingold -- Archives.; International Conference on Private Law Affecting Air Questions.; Aircraft accidents.; Aeronautics -- Law and legislation.; Aeronautics -- Safety measures.; Aeronautics, Commercial -- United States.; Aeronautics, Commercial -- Law and legislation.; Law firms -- United States.; Liability for aircraft accidents -- Law and legislation.; Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence.; Depositions.; Memorandums.; Press releases.; Law firms.; Aeronautics.; Transportation.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Speiser, Shumate, Geoghan, Krause & Rheingold, 1971.
Inventory
- Case files
  See also 1972 additions, below.
  - Aloha Airlines, Honolulu, Ha
    - General
      - Civil Aeronautics Board Accident Report, 1967 (Box 1)
  - American Flyers, Ardmore, Okla. (SA-392), 1966
    - General
      - Civil Aeronautics Board Hearing
        - Exhibits
          - Miscellaneous (Box 1)
          - 2A-11A18, 8 folders (Box 1)
        - Memoranda (Box 1)
  - Breslau v. Mohawk Airlines Inc. (SA-374)
    - General
      - Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 2)
      - Associated Cases: Schink v. Mohawk Airlines Inc., 1970 (Box 2)
      - Civil Aeronautics Board
        - Accident Report, 1964 (Box 2)
        - Hearing
          - Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 2)
          - Exhibits lA-9B, 10 folders (Box 2)
          - Exhibits 10A-P (Box 2)
          - Transcript Vols. 1-4, 4 folders (Box 3)
        - Conference with Hon. J.M. Canella (Box 3)
    - Evidence
      - Depositions
        - Baker, Robert C., 1965; 2 folders (Box 4)
        - Benscoter, Carl A., 1965 (Box 4)
        - Capp, William C., 1965 (Box 4)
        - Chapman, Claude W., 1964 (Box 4)
        - Curtis, Richard L., 1965 (Box 4)
        - DiStasio, Carl A., 1965; 2 folders (Box 4)
        - Doyle, James F., 1965 (Box 5)
        - Harrar, Robert G., 1965 (Box 5)
        - Holmes, Herbert H., 1965 (Box 5)
        - Howell, Robert A., 1965 (Box 5)
        - Loudin, Donald J., 1965; 2 folders (Box 5)
        - Mahoney, John F., 1965 (Box 5)
        - McIntyre, Charles J., 1965; 2 folders (Box 5)
        - Miara, Mary Ann, 1965 (Box 5)
        - Murray, Patrick J., 1965 (Box 6)
        - Nys, Andrew D., 1966 (Box 6)
        - Peach, Robert E., 1965 (Box 6)
        - Philler, William J., 1965 (Box 6)
        - Salato, Charles A., 1964 (Box 6)
        - Shimel, Richard E., 1965 (Box 6)
        - Silvera, Herbert, 1964 (Box 6)
        - Sufrin, Charles L. (Box 6)
        - Thorp, Robert B. (Box 6)
        - Throp, Robert B., 1964 (Box 7)
        - Wagner, Loren E., 1964 (Box 7)
        - Williams, John M., 1964 (Box 7)
      - Exhibits
        - Unnumbered (Box 7)
  - Craig v. Eastern Air Lines Inc., et al (SA-381)
    See also Case files, 1972 additions: SA-381, Eastern Airlines DC-7 Jones Beach, N.Y. crash.
    - General
      - Miscellaneous (Box 7)
      - Civil Aeronautics Board
        - Accident report (Box 7)
        - Hearing
          - Exhibit 6-F (Box 7)
          - Transcript, Vols. 1-4,1A, 4 folders (Box 7)
      - Discovery, 1966 (Box 8)
      - Memoranda, 1966 (Box 8)
      - Research materials (Box 8)
    - Evidence
      - Depositions
        - Eastern Air Lines Inc. by Robert S. Kraskey, 1967; 2 folders (Box 8)
        - Pan American World Airways Inc.
          - by Byron C. Bryant, 1966; 2 folders (Box 8)
          - by Terrence J. Cannon, 1966 (Box 8)
          - by Robert A. Marshall, 1966 (Box 8)
          - by Robert A. Marshall, 1966; 3 folders (Box 9)
        - United States of America
          - by Peter Angelone, 1966 (Box 9)
          - by Peter Angelone, 1966 (Box 10)
          - by Eugene Assip, 1966 (Box 10)
          - by Bernard C. Doyle, 1966 (Box 10)
          - by Raynor Lockwood Duncombe, 1966 (Box 10)
          - by Joseph E. Evans, 1966 (Box 10)
          - by Charles F. Flohr, 1967; 3 folders (Box 10)
          - by Frederick Fritz, 1966 (Box 11)
          - by William C. Keepers, 1966; 3 folders (Box 11)
          - by Thomas J. McKelvey, 1966 (Box 11)
          - by Louis S. Natale, 1966 (Box 11)
          - by William Papadeas, 1966 (Box 12)
          - by Raymond L. Schulze, 1966 (Box 12)
          - by Wayne L. Siebert, 1966 (Box 12)
          - by John D. Zagami, 1966; 3 folders (Box 12)
      - Exhibits
        - Unnumbered, 2 folders (Box 12)
        - Unnumbered, 5 folders (Box 13)
  - Cramer v. United Air Lines Inc., et al (SA-380)
    - General
      - Miscellaneous (Box 13)
      - Civil Aeronautics Board Hearing
        - Accident report, 1966 (Box 13)
        - Hearing
          - Exhibits
            - Miscellaneous, 9 folders (Box 13)
            - 1A-8L, 9 folders (Box 13)
            - 9A-28A, 12 folders (Box 14)
        - Transcript, Vols. 1-2A, 4 folders (Box 14)
        - Transcript, Vols. 3-5, 1965; 3 folders (Box 15)
      - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 15)
      - Discovery, 1967
        - Notice (Box 15)
        - Stipulation (Box 15)
        - United Air Lines (Box 15)
        - Vickers Holding Ltd. (Box 15)
    - Evidence
      - Depositions
        - Adkins, Minnis Benton, 1968 (Box 15)
        - Anderson, Joe H., 1967 (Box 15)
        - Bannister, Geoffrey Thomas, 1968 (Box 15)
        - Bible, Hugh, 1967 (Box 15)
        - Brown, Harold, 1967 (Box 15)
        - Collins, Richard Augusta, Jr., 1968; 2 folders (Box 15)
        - Davis, Warren L., 1968 (Box 15)
        - Dudley, Frank, 1968 (Box 15)
        - Finck, Dr. Pierre A., 1969 (Box 15)
        - Gormley, Joseph Leo, 1969 (Box 16)
        - Griffin, Marvin R., 1969 (Box 16)
        - Grimes, Corwin C., 1969 (Box 16)
        - Hall, Bryte Baker, 1969 (Box 16)
        - Helwig, Elson B., 1969 (Box 16)
        - Henneges, Elaine, 1968 (Box 16)
        - Hill, Judy, 1967 (Box 16)
        - Holshouser, William L., 1969; 2 folders (Box 16)
        - Huff, William, 1967 (Box 16)
        - Huntington, Samuel Lee, 1968 (Box 16)
        - Johnson, Glenn, 1967 (Box 16)
        - Kenlan, Richard J., 1968; 3 folders (Box 16)
        - Leroy, C. Hayden, 1969 (Box 16)
        - Leslie, Alfred W., 1968; 2 folders (Box 17)
        - Love, Charles F., 1967 (Box 17)
        - Madgwick, Thomas, 1969 (Box 17)
        - Ottinger, Johnny C., 1967 (Box 17)
        - Reed, Roy C., 1967 (Box 17)
        - Smelcer, Betty Jo, 1967 (Box 17)
        - Smelcer, William E., 1967 (Box 17)
        - Smith, James B., 1969 (Box 17)
        - Smith, Lofton, 1967 (Box 17)
        - Wilhoit, Helen, 1967 (Box 17)
        - Zeffert, Harry, 1969 (Box 17)
      - Exhibits, unnumbered, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Holtzman, et al v. British European Airway Corp
    - General
      - Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 18)
    - Evidence
      - Depositions, 1968
        - Atkins, William (Box 18)
        - Baillie, William (Box 18)
        - Brinjes, Dennis G. (Box 18)
        - Fisher, Charles T. (Box 18)
        - Gordon-Burge, Hubert K. (Box 18)
        - Jupe, Cecil A. (Box 18)
        - Lett, James H. (Box 18)
        - Wilkins, Charles T. (Box 18)
        - Wyld, Robert W. (Box 18)
      - Exhibits (Box 18)
  - Howard and Love v. Pakistan International Airlines
    - General
      - Miscellaneous (Box 18)
      - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 18)
    - Evidence
      - Exhibits, unnumbered, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Marsi v. United States of America v. Greylock Airways Inc. et al
    - General
      - Interrogatories
        - 1967-1969, 5 folders (Box 19)
        - 1968 (Box 20)
      - Motions, 1968-1969; 4 folders (Box 20)
      - Pleadings, 1967-1968; 3 folders (Box 20)
      - Pleadings, 1968-1969; 4 folders (Box 21)
  - Northeast Airlines, Hanover, New Hampshire (SA-408)
    - General
      - National Transportation Safety Board of Inquiry
        - Transcripts, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 21)
        - Transcripts, Vols. 3-4, 1961; 2 folders (Box 22)
  - Pearson and Trauth v. Northeast Airlines (SA-335)
    - General
      - Correspondence (Box 22)
      - Civil Aeronautics Board hearing
        - Exhibits
          - Unnumbered, 2 folders (Box 22)
          - 10A-1-11A-4, 2 folders (Box 22)
          - 12A-1-13A-8 Box 24, 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Ruggard v. Eastern Airlines Inc., et al (SA-379)
    - General
      - Miscellaneous (Box 23)
      - Civil Aeronautics Board Hearing
        - Transcript, Vols. 1-5, 1964; 5 folders (Box 23)
        - Transcript, Vol. 6, 1964 (Box 24)
      - Memoranda, 1965 (Box 24)
    - Evidence
      - Depositions
        - Appleget, Capt. A.V. (Box 24)
        - Douglas Aircraft Co., Inc.
          - by Michael Bates, 1967 (Box 24)
          - by John M. Divola, 1968 (Box 24)
          - by Orville R. Dumm, 1967; 2 folders (Box 24)
          - by Arnold Heimerdinger, 1967; 2 folders (Box 25)
          - by Herbert E. Morphew, 1967 (Box 25)
          - by Roger D. Schaufele, 2 folders (Box 25)
          - by Richard P. Schlitz, 1967 (Box 25)
        - McGill, Paul M. (Box 25)
        - Smith, Norman C. (Box 25)
      - Exhibits
        - List (Box 25)
        - First Series, 1-5, 5 folders (Box 25)
        - First Series, 6-37, 21 folders (Box 26)
        - Second Series, 1.2.4.6-11, 13, 10 folders (Box 26)
        - Second Series, 14-16, 21, 23-25, 27, 29, 32, 10 folders (Box 27)
        - Unnumbered, 2 folders (Box 27)
        - Unnumbered, 5 folders (Box 28)
        - Unnumbered, 4 folders (Box 29)
        - Unnumbered, 4 folders (Box 30)
        - Unnumbered, 6 folders (Box 31)
        - Unnumbered (Box 32)
  - Saari v. Ritchey
    - General
      - Miscellaneous (Box 32)
      - Correspondence (Box 32)
      - National Transportation Safety Board Report (Box 32)
      - Pleadings (Box 32)
  - Sardelle v. British Aircraft Corp. et al. (SA-399)
    - General
      - Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 32)
      - Discovery, 1970 (Box 32)
      - Memoranda (Box 32)
      - National Transportation Safety Board of Inquiry
        - Exhibits
          - List (Box 32)
          - 1A-6A, 3 folders (Box 32)
          - 7A-12A, 3 folders (Box 33)
        - Transcript, 1967; 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Evidence
      - Depositions
        - British Aircraft Corporation
          - by Jack Brunning, 1970; 3 folders (Box 33)
          - by Jack Brunning, 1970; 3 folders (Box 34)
          - by David James, 1970; 4 folders (Box 34)
          - by Harry Zeffert, 1970 (Box 34)
          - by Harry Zeffert, 1970; 2 folders (Box 35)
        - Garrett Corp., by S.J. Baczynski, 1970; 2 folders (Box 35)
        - Schumacher, Mark (Box 35)
      - Exhibits
        - Unnumbered, 3 folders (Box 35)
        - Unnumbered, 7 folders (Box 36)
        - Unnumbered, 5 folders (Box 37)
        - Unnumbered, 5 folders (Box 38)
        - Unnumbered, 8 folders (Box 39)
        - Unnumbered, 5 folders (Box 40)
  - Trans-Canada Airlines, Ste. Therese de Blainville, P.Q.
    - General
      - Commission of Inquiry
        - Report (Box 40)
        - Transcript, 4 folders (Box 40)
        - Transcript, 1964; 5 folders (Box 41)
  - Trans-World and Eastern Airlines, Carmel, N.Y. (SA-389)
    - General
      - Civil Aeronautics Board Hearing
        - Deposition, by Holt, Roger, 1966 (Box 41)
        - Transcript, Vols. 1-3, 1965-1966; 14 folders (Box 41)
        - Transcript, Vol. 2, 1965 (Box 42)
  - Wright et al. v. British Aircraft Corp and Braniff Airways (SA-393)
    - General
      - Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 42)
      - Accident reports
        - Air Line Pilots Association, 1966 (Box 42)
        - Braniff Airways, Inc., 1968 (Box 42)
        - British Aircraft Corp., Ltd., 1967 (Box 42)
      - Change of venue (Box 42)
      - Clippings, 1966-1968 (Box 42)
      - Correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box 42)
      - Discovery
        - Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 42)
        - Conferences with Hon. S. Sugarman, 1968 (Box 42)
        - Documents requested (Box 42)
        - London BAC documents (Box 42)
        - Notes (Box 42)
        - Orders (Box 42)
      - Memoranda, 1966-1969 (Box 42)
      - National Transportation Safety Board Report, 1968 (Box 42)
      - Technical information file
        - Miscellaneous, 1965-1967 (Box 42)
        - Auto-Pilot System, 1966 (Box 43)
        - Force Limiter Spring (Box 43)
        - Graphs, 1966 (Box 43)
        - Hydraulic System (Box 43)
        - Hydraulic System Filters (Box 43)
        - Maps, 1966 (Box 43)
        - Rudder Control System (Box 43)
        - Rudder Feel Unit Linkage (Box 43)
        - Series Yaw Damper (Box 43)
        - Spoiler/Speed Brake System (Box 43)
        - Sticking Valve Problems (Box 43)
    - Evidence
      - Depositions
        - Orders, 1966-1969 (Box 43)
        - Achilles, Frank L. Jr., 1968; 3 folders (Box 43)
        - Ashcroft, Grace, 1966 (Box 43)
        - Braniff Airways, Inc.
          - by John H. Cope, 1968 (Box 43)
          - by S.F. Herod, 2 folders (Box 43)
        - Brown, Bernard David, 1968 (Box 44)
        - Cheetham, Capt. George, 1968; 2 folders (Box 44)
        - Cope, Capt. James (Box 44)
        - Corrigan, Matt (Box 44)
        - Flume, Richard, 1968; 2 folders (Box 44)
        - Harris, Robert P., 1968; 2 folders (Box 44)
        - Harvey, Albert, 1968; 2 folders (Box 44)
        - Hitch, Henry P.Y. (Box 44)
        - Holmback, Glenn E., 1968; 2 folders (Box 45)
        - Hudson, Capt. James, 1968; 2 folders (Box 45)
        - Hughes, Dan Jr., 1968 (Box 45)
        - Jackson, Dennis, 1968; 5 folders (Box 45)
        - James, David, 1968-1969; 6 folders (Box 46)
        - Keith, Homer William, 1968; 4 folders (Box 46)
        - Kraus, Edmund, 1971 (Box 46)
        - Kreimer, Capt. Edward P., 1968; 2 folders (Box 47)
        - Lambert, Derek (Box 47)
        - Lawson, Kenneth S., 1969; 3 folders (Box 47)
        - Marsh, Peter, 1969 (Box 47)
        - Montgomery, Geoffrey N., 1968 (Box 47)
        - Powell, Gordon, 1969; 5 folders (Box 47)
        - Powell, Gordon, 1969 (Box 48)
        - Prosser, Norman, 1969 (Box 48)
        - Rock, Francis C., 1971 (Box 48)
        - Sawyer, Robert, 1968; 6 folders (Box 48)
        - Steele, E.A., 1969; 3 folders (Box 49)
        - Sweitzer, Capt. Robert J., 1968; 2 folders (Box 49)
        - Watson, Arthur C, 1968; 2 folders (Box 49)
        - White, Murry, 1968; 3 folders (Box 49)
      - Exhibits
        - Miscellaneous (Box 50)
        - Listings (Box 50)
        - 1-1, Vols. 1-3, 3 folders (Box 50)
        - 1-1, Vol. 4 (Box 51)
        - 1-2, Vols. 1-3, 3 folders (Box 51)
        - 1-3, Vols. 1-3, 3 folders (Box 52)
        - 1-4, Vol. 2 (Box 52)
        - 1-4, Vols. 3-4, 2 folders (Box 53)
        - 1-5, Vol. 1 (Box 53)
        - 1-5, Vols. 2-3, 2 folders (Box 54)
        - 1-6, Vol.3 (Box 54)
        - 1-7, Vol. 1 (Box 54)
        - 1-7 Vols. 2-3, 2 folders (Box 55)
        - 1-8, Vols. 1-3, 3 folders (Box 55)
        - 2-1, Vol. 2 (Box 56)
        - 2-2, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 56)
        - 3-1, Vol. 1 (Box 56)
        - 3-1, Vol. 2 (Box 57)
        - 3-2 and 3-3, 2 folders (Box 57)
        - 4-1, Vol. 1 (Box 57)
        - 4-1, Vols. 2-3, 2 folders (Box 58)
        - 4-2, Vol. 1 (Box 58)
        - 4-2, Vols. 2-3, 2 folders (Box 59)
        - 4-3, Vol. 1 (Box 59)
        - 4-3, Vols. 2-3, 2 folders (Box 60)
        - 4-4, Vol. 1 (Box 60)
        - 4-4, Vols. 2-3, 2 folders (Box 61)
        - 4-5, Vol. 1 (Box 61)
        - 4-5, Vol. 2 (Box 62)
        - 4-6, Vols. 1-3, 3 folders (Box 62)
        - 4-7, Vols. 1-3, 3 folders (Box 63)
        - 4-8, Vols. 1-3, 3 folders (Box 64)
        - 4-9, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 64)
        - 4-9, Vols. 3-4, 2 folders (Box 65)
        - 4-10, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 65)
        - 4-10, Vol. 3 (Box 66)
        - 4-11, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 66)
        - 4-12, Vols. 1-3, 3 folders (Box 67)
        - 4-13, Vol. 1 (Box 67)
        - 4-13, Vols. 2-3, 2 folders (Box 68)
        - 4-14, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 68)
        - 4-14, Vol. 3 (Box 69)
        - 4-15, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 69)
        - 4-16, Vol. 1 (Box 70)
        - 4-17 and 4-18 (Box 70)
        - 4-19, Vol. 1 (Box 71)
        - 4-20, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 71)
        - 4-21, Vol. 1 (Box 71)
        - 4-21, Vol. 1 (Box 72)
        - 4-22, Vol. 1 (Box 72)
        - 5-1, Vols. 1-3, 3 folders (Box 72)
        - 5-1, Vol. 4 (Box 73)
        - 5-2, Vols. 1-3, 3 folders (Box 73)
        - 5-3, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 74)
        - 5-4, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 74)
        - 5-4, Vols. 3-4, 2 folders (Box 75)
        - 6-1, Vol.1 (Box 75)
        - 6-2, Vol. 1 (Box 75)
        - 6-3, Vol. 1 (Box 75)
        - 6-4, Vol.1 (Box 76)
        - 7-1, Vol. 1 (Box 76)
        - 7-2, Vol. 1 (Box 76)
        - 7-3, Vol. 1 (Box 76)
        - 7-3, Vol.2 (Box 77)
        - 7-4, Vol.1 (Box 77)
        - 7-5, Vol.1 (Box 77)
        - 7-6, Vol.1 (Box 78)
        - 7-7, Vol.1 (Box 78)
        - 7-8, Vol.1 (Box 78)
        - 7-9, Vol.1 (Box 78)
        - 7-10, Vol.1 (Box 78)
        - 7-11, Vol. 1 (Box 78)
        - 7-12, Vol.1 (Box 79)
        - 7-13, Vol.1 (Box 79)
        - 7-14, Vol.1 (Box 79)
        - 7-17, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 79)
        - 8-1, Vol. 1, 2 folders (Box 80)
        - 8-2, Vol. 1 (Box 80)
        - 8-3, Vol. 1 (Box 81)
        - 8-4, Vol. 1 (Box 81)
        - 9-1 (Box 81)
        - 9-2 (Box 81)
        - 9-3 (Box 82)
        - 10 (Box 82)
        - 11-1 Vols. 2-3, 2 folders (Box 82)
        - 11-2 Vol.1 (Box 82)
        - 11-2, Vol.2 (Box 83)
        - 11-3, Vol.1 (Box 83)
        - 11-4, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 83)
        - 11-5 (Box 84)
        - 11-6, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 84)
        - 11-7 and 11-8, 2 folders (Box 84)
        - 11-9 and 11-10, 2 folders (Box 85)
        - 11-11, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 85)
        - 11-12, Vol. 1 (Box 85)
        - 11-12, Vol.2 (Box 86)
        - 11-13, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 86)
        - 11-14, Vol.1 (Box 87)
        - 11-15, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 87)
        - 11-16, Vol. 1 (Box 87)
        - 11-16, Vol. 2 (Box 88)
        - 11-17, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 88)
        - 11-18 (Box 88)
        - 11-19, Vol. 1 (Box 88)
        - 11-19, Vol. 2 (Box 89)
        - 11-20, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 89)
        - 11-21 (Box 89)
        - 11-22 to 11-25, 4 folders (Box 90)
        - 12-1, Vol. 1 (Box 91)
        - 12-2, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 91)
        - 12-3, Vol. 1 (Box 92)
        - 13-1, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 92)
        - 13-2, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 93)
        - 14, Vol. 1 (Box 93)
        - 15-1, Vol. 1 (Box 93)
        - 15-2, Vol. 1 (Box 93)
        - 15-3, Vol. 1 (Box 93)
        - 15-4, Vol. 1 (Box 94)
        - 15-5, Vol. 1 (Box 94)
        - 15-6, Vol. 1 (Box 94)
        - 16-1, Vol. 1 (Box 94)
        - 16-2, Vol. 1 (Box 94)
        - 17-3, Vol. 1 (Box 94)
        - 17-4, Vol. 1 (Box 94)
        - 17-5, Vol.1 (Box 94)
        - 18, Vol. 1 (Box 94)
        - 18, Vol.2 (Box 95)
        - 19-1, Vols. 1-3, 3 folders (Box 95)
        - 19-1, Vol. 4 (Box 96)
        - 19-2, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 96)
        - 20-1, Vols. 1-2, 3 folders (Box 97)
        - 20-2, Vols. 1-3, 3 folders (Box 98)
        - 20-2, Vol.4 (Box 99)
        - 20-3, Vols. 1-3, 3 folders (Box 99)
        - 20-3, Vol. 4 (Box 100)
        - 20-4, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 100)
        - 20-4, Vols. 3-4, 2 folders (Box 101)
        - 20-5, Vol.1 (Box 101)
        - 20-5, Vol. 2 (Box 102)
        - 20-6, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 102)
        - 20-7, Vols. 1-3, 3 folders (Box 103)
        - 21, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 104)
        - 22, Vol. 1 (Box 104)
        - 22, Vol. 2 (Box 105)
        - 23-1, Vol.1 (Box 105)
        - 23-2, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 105)
        - 23-3, Vol.1 (Box 105)
        - 23-4, Vol. 1 (Box 106)
        - 24, Vol. 1 (Box 106)
        - 25, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 106)
        - 26 (Box 107)